Capital Bicycle Club 057
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Capital Bicycle Club Collection
1880-1929
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Capital Bicycle Club
057
4 Linear feet
10 Boxes
Arrangement
Series 1: Photographs, 1 linear foot (1882-1890) The series consists of photographs of the Capital Bicycle Club and it's members from 1882-1890. The Series is arranged chronologically by date and event featuring both group and individual shots. Club members Clarence G. Allen, L. Warren Seely, Herbert S. "Bert" Owen, and Max Hansmann are prominently featured. The reverse of the photographs notes members, dates, locations, and specific activities. The series also contains reproductions of the club's original photographs by the Star newspaper for an article documenting the club's history printed sometime in 1926, which include two mounted rotogravures.
Series 2: Memorabilia, 3.5 linear feet (1880-1929) The series consists of scrapbooks and assorted clippings, papers, and programs of the Capital Bicycle Club and it's members from 1880-1929. The series contains the club's official scrapbook (1880-1890) and a scrapbook prepared by the D.C. Public Library (1891-1929). Each scrapbook is chronologically arranged by date and contains clippings, prize ribbons, and programs. Of special note is founding member L. Warren Seely's original manuscript for the "Presentation of the Cat", circa 1883. A corresponding transcript is included in the series from The Republic's January 27, 1883 issue.
Series 3: Official Records, 4 linear feet (1881-1911) The series consists of the official records of the Capital Bicycle Club from 1881-1911. A list of officers for each year is included in the records as well as the club's official meeting minutes as recorded by the Secretary. The series also contains copies of the Executive Committee's official correspondence from 1886-1890.
Biographical / Historical
On January 31, 1879 Herbert S. "Bert" Owen, Max Hansmann, F.D. Owen, L.P. Einolf, F.G. Wood, L.N. Jessunofsy, and Charles Krauskopf founded the Capital Bicycle Club on the steps of the United States Capitol. The Club was the third of its kind in the United States and was incorporated on May 6, 1886 with the motto "Swiftly and Silently". The initial goal of the Club was to affect public perception of the bicycle by working with local officials on safety measures. As part of Club rules, members were instructed to use bells during the day and lamps at night to avoid collisions with pedestrians. Such measures secured local rights for Club members, and wheelmen in general, while influencing new municipal bicycle policies across the United States. Major Thomas P. Morgan of the Metropolitan Police Department was an honorary member.
The Club members were mostly professional men who devoted much time and money to bicycling. The first meetings were held in members' homes, but growth caused club members to rent a space on 10th Street NW near H Street. In 1880 the Club moved to 412 11th Street NW. In 1882 the Club moved to 919 G Street NW for two years until the federal government bought the building for office space. The Club then decided to finance the construction of its own building at 409 15th Street NW and ground broke on May 18th 1886.
Club members organized many expeditions throughout D.C., Maryland, and Virginia; including tours of the Natural Bridge in 1882 and Cabin John Bridge in 1884. Individual members were nationally recognized for advanced riding techniques. The Club also participated in collegial races. On June 29, 1880 the Club's first annual races were held at Iowa Circle (later renamed Logan Circle) and by 1883 the Club laid a track at Athletic Park at 9th and S Streets NW. The Athletic Park was the site of the 5th Annual League of American Wheelmen Races on May 20, 1884.
Although bicycling was the main focus, Club members took part in many other social activities including banquets, a bicycle debating society, and a camera club, which sponsored America's first photography salon the "Washington Salon and Art Photographic Exhibition" in 1896.
The Club disbanded in 1912. Surviving members continued to hold annual events including the "61st Capital Bicycle Club Birthday" celebration held on January 31, 1940.
Custodial History
The original donor of the photographs is not known. Part of the collection consists of photographs transferred from the Historic Image Collection. Other photographs have a stamp on the back reading "Public Library November 16, 1951, Washingtoniana", and few others in Series 1 are stamped with "Clarence G. Allen, Ontario. Apt. 601. Tel. Col. 800". Clarence G. Allen was an active member of the Capital Bicycle Club. A scrapbook in Series 2 was created by the D.C. Public Library and documents the activities of the Capital Bicycle Club from 1891-1929.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains items of the Capital Bicycle Club dating from 1880 to 1929, and includes 126 photographs, two scrapbooks, and five record books. The photographs are of the Club's events including the 5th Annual League of American Wheelman Races on May 20, 1884 and Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run on May 7, 1888. Also included are member portraits from the 1880's by professional photography studios and founding member Max Hansmann cyanotype images. The two scrapbooks span the years 1880-1929 and include clippings from The Wheelman and Club member L.Warren Seely's original manuscript for the "Presentation of the Cat". Series 1 includes pictorial documentation of the "Procession of the Sacred Cat", held in 1887 with club members dressed in costumes. Record books include correspondence, meeting minutes, and other official records, begin in October of 1881 and end in July of 1911.
Sports; Bicycles; Athletic clubs; Societies and clubs; Pennsylvania Quarter (Washington, D.C.); Photographs; Scrapbooks; Ephemera
- Series 1: Photographs, 1882-1890
  Scope and Contents
  The series consists of photographs of the Capital Bicycle Club and it's members from 1882-1890. The series is arranged chronologically by date and event featuring both group and individual shots. Club members Clarence G. Allen, L. Warren Seely, Herbert S. "Bert" Owen, and Max Hansmann are prominently featured. The reverse of the photographs notes members, dates, locations, and specific activities. The 5th Annual League of American Wheelmen Races on May 20, 1884 and Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run on May 7, 1888 were photographed heavily. The "Procession of the Sacred Cat" on February 22, 1887 features some very interesting photographs of club members in costume. Max Hansmann was the primary photographer for the club and applied the popular cyanotype development method to many of the photographs, which gives them a blue tint. Cyanotype photographs are noted in the folder description along with available corresponding negatives from the Washington, D.C. Historic Image Collection. The series also contains reproductions of the club's original photographs by the Star newspaper for an article documenting the club's history printed sometime in 1926, which include two mounted rotogravures. Rotogravure is an early photomechanical process of printing photographs in newspapers. A copy of the Star article can be found in the collection's vertical file.
  - Natural Bridge Tour - C. Allen/M. Hansmann/L.W. Seely (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 14020), September 1882 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Natural Bridge Tour - C. Allen/M. Hansmann/L.W. Seely (photograph by Max Hansmann - duplicate - negative 14020), September 1882 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Natural Bridge Tour - C. Allen/L.W. Seely/M. Hansmann (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 14028), September 1882 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Natural Bridge Tour - C. Allen, September 1882 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Small mounted photo prints of Natural Bridge Tour - (photographs by Max Hansmann - no negative), September 1882 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Clubhouse - 919 G Street N.W. - Exterior group shot (photographer unknown - no negative), 1882-1884 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "The Collision" (photographer unknown - negative 6336), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - Polo Games (photographer unknown - negative 6337), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - LAW Races (photographer unknown - negative 6338), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "The Stack" (photographer unknown - negative 6339), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "The March" (photographer unknown - negative 6340), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - LAW Races (photographer unknown - negative 6341), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - LAW Races (photographer unknown - negative 6342), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 1 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6343), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 3 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6344), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "Finley fancy riding on Star" (photographer unknown - negative 6345), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "Finley fancy riding on Star – Backward in Saddle" (photographer unknown - negative 6346), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "Finley and Chickering on Star – Head Down" (photographer unknown - negative 6347), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "Finley and Chickering on Star" (photographer unknown - negative 6348), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "A Shooting Star" Rex Smith riding down Capitol Steps (photographer unknown - negative 6349), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "Parade of the Capital Club – The March" (photographer unknown - negative 6350), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "Finley fancy riding on Star" (photographer unknown - negative 6351), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "Finley fancy riding on Star (before steering rod on one foot)" (photographer unknown - negative 6352), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 5 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6353), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 1 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6354), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 3 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6355), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 10 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6356), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 5 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6357), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "Parade of the Capital Bicycle Club – The Stack" (photographer unknown - negative 6358), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 3 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6359), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 1 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6360), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 25 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6361), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "LAW Parade Review in front of Arlington Hotel" (photographer unknown - negative 6362), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "LAW Parade - May 1884 - Capital Bicycle Club parading in front of Arlington Hotel" (photographer unknown - negative 4086), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 10 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6363), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 25 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6364), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "Close Quarters" (photographer unknown - negative 6365), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - Unknown (photographer unknown - negative 6366), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 1 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6367), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - "Rex Smith riding on one wheel standing in saddle" (photographer unknown - negative 6368), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 1 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6369), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. - 3 Mile Race (photographer unknown - negative 6370), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. (Cyanotypes) - "Club Races" (photographer unknown - negative 7558), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. (Cyanotypes) - "The Finish" (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 7562), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. (Cyanotypes) - Unknown (photographer unknown - negative 7563), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. (Cyanotypes) - "The Finish" (photograph by Max Hansmann - no negative), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - League of American Wheelmen - Washington Athletic Park - 9th and S Streets N.W. (Cyanotypes) - Unknown (photograph by Max Hansmann - no negative), May 20 1884 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Cabin John Bridge - C. Allen - L.W. Seely - M. Hansmann (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 9233), 1884 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Cabin John Bridge- C. Allen - L.W. Seely - M. Hansmann (photograph by Max Hansmann - duplicate - negative 9233), 1884 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Cabin John Bridge - C. Allen - L.W. Seely - M. Hansmann (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - negative 9290), 1884 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Will Robertson and Rex Smith on Capitol Steps - Will Robertson (photographer unknown - negative 154620), 1884 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Will Robertson and Rex Smith on Capitol Steps - Rex Smith (photographer unknown - negative 8068), 1884 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Portrait of Herbert S. "Bert" Owen - "First man to ride down Capitol Steps" (photographer unknown - negative 9227), 1885 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Capital Outing to Martha's Vineyard - Massachusetts - Group shot - Clubhouse 919 G Street N.W. (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - negative 9289), August 1885 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - New Clubhouse - 409 15th Street N.W. (Cyanotypes) - Group shot - "Site of new clubhouse" (photographer unknown - no negative), May 18 1886 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - New Clubhouse - 409 15th Street N.W. (Cyanotypes) - Group shot - "Laying the clubhouse cornerstone" (photograph by Max Hansmann - no negative), 1886 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - New Clubhouse - 409 15th Street N.W. (Cyanotypes) - Group shot - "Setting the Keystone of Arch" (photographer unknown- no negative), 1886 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - New Clubhouse - 409 15th Street N.W. (Cyanotypes) - Group shot - "Laying corner stone" (photograph by Max Hansmann - no negative), 1886 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Procession of the Sacred Cat - Group shot (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 6374), February 22 1887 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Procession of the Sacred Cat -Group shot (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 6376), February 22 1887 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Procession of the Sacred Cat - Group shot (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - no negative), February 22 1887 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Procession of the Sacred Cat - Group shot (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - no negative), February 22 1887 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Procession of the Sacred Cat - Group shot (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - negative 8250), February 22 1887 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Procession of the Sacred Cat - Group shot (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - no negative), February 22 1887 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "Entering Cosmopolitan Club Park" (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 6294), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "Entering Cosmopolitan Club Park" (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - negative 6294), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "Entering Cosmopolitan Club Park" (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 6295), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "Entering Cosmopolitan Club Park" (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - negative 6295), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "The Crowd – Cosmopolitan Club Park" (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 6296), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "The Crowd – Cosmopolitan Club Park" (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - negative 6296), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "Ready for Bert Owen's Birthday Run: he at head of line" (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 6371), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "Ready for Bert Owen's Birthday Run: he at head of line" (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - negative 6371), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "Start from Capital Bicycle Club's House" (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - no negative), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "The Crowd – Cosmopolitan Club Park" (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 6372), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "The Crowd – Cosmopolitan Club Park" (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - negative 6372), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "The Start" (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 6373), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "The Parade – Brightwood" (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 6375), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "The Celebrated Cow-Boy Band" (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 6378), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "The Crowd – Cosmopolitan Club Park" (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 6379), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "Follow-my-leader - Followers in trouble" (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - negative 7559), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "Follow-me-leader – No trouble for Bert" (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - negative 7560), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "Follow-my-leader – A follower in trouble" (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - no negative), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - Unknown (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - negative 7938), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "Follow-my-leader – A follower in trouble" (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 7984), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "Follow-my-leader – The Ravine" (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - no negative), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen's Birthday Run - "Follow-my-leader – The Ravine" (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - no negative), May 7 1888 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Capital Bicycle ClubHouse - Exterior shot (photograph by Max Hansmann - cyanotype - negative 154419), 1889 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Capital Bicycle ClubHouse - Exterior shot (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 154649), 1889 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Capital Bicycle ClubHouse - Hall and Reading Room of Clubhouse (photograph by Max Hansmann - no negative), 1889 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Capital Bicycle ClubHouse - Exterior shot (photograph by Max Hansmann - no negative), 1889 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Capital Bicycle ClubHouse - Exterior shot (photograph by Max Hansmann - negative 6511), 1889 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Portraits – 1880's - Wallace Crossman (G.W. Davis Photograph Studio- negative 824) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Portraits – 1880's - Herbert S. "Bert" Owen (The American Photographic Studio- negative 1190) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Portraits – 1880's - Unknown (Gen. Prince Artistic Portraits- negative 6320) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Portraits – 1880's - Abner Y. Dunnington (Clinedinst Studios- negative 6321), Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Portraits – 1880's - Unknown (photographer unknown - negative 6322), Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Portraits – 1880's - Unknown (photographer unknown - negative 6323), Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Portraits – 1880's - Clarence G. Allen (G.W. Davis- negative 6324), Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Portraits – 1880's - W.F. Morsell (Rice Studio- negative 6325), Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Portraits – 1880's - E.H. Fowler (photographer unknown - negative 6326), Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Portraits – 1880's - George Ruoff (Rice Studio- negative 6327), Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Portraits – 1880's - C.H. Wilkins (photographer unknown - negative 6328), 1883 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Portraits – 1880's - J. West Wagner (photographer unknown - negative 6329), Undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Portraits – 1880's - Geu. A. Warren (N.Y. Photo Co.- negative 6330), 1884 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Portraits – 1880's - Portrait unknown (Johnson Bros. Studios- negative 6331), Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Portraits – 1880's - Portrait unknown (E. Glenton Studio- negative 6332), Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Portraits – 1880's - Portrait unknown (G. W. Davis- negative 6333), Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Portraits – 1880's - Portrait unknown (photographer unknown - negative 6334), Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Portraits – 1880's - John Sevinborne (G. W. Davis- no negative), 1881 (Box 2, Folder 45)